BOGDAN RUDENKO

Full-stack developer

CONTACT

+382 68 430 655

lurkingbo@gmail.com

https://rudenko.digital

https://linkedin.com/in/lurkingbo

LOCATION

Budva, Montenegro

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Moscow Technical University Of Communications And Informatics

2013-2017

SKILLS

TypeScript, JavaScript,

React, React-Native, Expo, Recoil,

Mobx, Apollo, Graphql,

Node.js, Nest.js, PostgreSQL,

SQLite, TypeORM

LANGUAGES

Russian - Native

English - B2

Montenegrin/Serbian - A1

SUMMARY

A passionate web developer with over 5 years experience in creating stable and modern web applications. Would be glad to share my experience and eager to solve more complex problems and continue to find ways to maximize user efficiency.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MIDDLE FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Astra Healt Tech LLC

2022 - 2023

- Initiated migration from legacy aproches, like class containers in React to hooks
- Made some improvements in app performance.
 Decreased rerenders count
- Led meetings and participate in app performance optimisation discussions

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Digitarium LLC

2021 - 2022

- Built UI from scratch and maintained existing, made a mobile application with React Native and Expo
- Led some meetings, announced some good ideas and as a result, some of them were implemented

JAVASCRIPT GAME DEVELOPER

Siberteam (Betsoft LLC)

2019 - 2021

- · Built games using selfmade javascript game engine
- Made sprites with Photoshop & After Effects
- SVN as version control system

JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

Deep 2000 LLC

2017 - 2019

- Built queue management systems with JQuery and React
- Made interfaces based on brandbooks with Photoshop
- TFS as version control system